I hold multiple industry certifications across Microsoft and Oracle.
I hold Microsoft certified credentials with a strong focus on cloud and AI technologies,
including Azure AI Fundamentals, Azure AI Engineer Associate,
Azure Administrator Associate, and Power Platform Fundamentals.
I am also certified in Oracle Cloud Infrastructure,
covering architect associate, multi-cloud architecture,
generative AI, AI Foundations, Cloud Foundations,
Data Management Foundations, and the Sunbird Ed Specialty.
At the foundational level, I hold programming certifications in Python and JavaScript,
along with Neo4j Professional Certifications,
including Graph Data Science and Certified Professional.