My project experience includes the development of a personal protective equipment or PPE,
CCTV system, a computer vision solution using convolutional neural networks for real-time
PPE detection built with Python, YOLOv9, and Google Colab.
I also developed the ALOPA Corporation Chrome extension, which automates data transfer
from Google Sheets to web forms using Python, Selenium, Flask, and a custom Chrome extension.
Additionally, I worked on a predictive analytics project focused on forecasting food prices
through time series analysis using Orange Data Mining and the ARIMA model.
My AI projects include a local language generation application built with Python, LangChain,
the Hugging Face Mistral 7B model, as well as an AutoGPT application designed to extract
YouTube video transcripts and answer content-related questions.