Hi. I'm Miguel Lacanienta. Welcome to my portfolio.
Use the buttons above to walk through my Objective, Skills, Certifications, Applied Skills, and Projects.
Below are the projects themselves. Click any card to watch a narrated walkthrough.
DTR System. A full-stack daily-time record POC I built solo to prove AI can cut team cost.
PPE Detection. My thesis. Fine-tuned YOLO V9 flag safety violations in real-time via telegram.
Sheets to form automation. A Chrome extension that fills hundreds of web forms from a spreadsheet in one click.
Food Price Forecasting. A REMA time series models predicting Philippine food prices from WFP data.
Local LLM app. Mistral 7B running fully on device. No API keys. No cloud.
YouTube Q&A tool. A rag notebook that answers any question about a two-hour YouTube video.
RPSLS Game. Rock, Paper, Scissors, Lizard, Spock. Built for hundreds of players at Digital Day-to-day Manila.
HTTYD Telegram Bots. Dragon Character Bots for how to train your AI Dragon.
Hackathon Videos. Narrated entries for Recruit Bolt, Spec Sync, and R/Fact Checker on DevPost.
Genie Game. Voice Generation and Lip Sync for the Genie character at Inspire. That's the tour. Click anything to dive in.